nextsteptestprep.com 2019-12-13

# Privacy Policy

**What information do we collect?**

We collect information from you when you register on our site or subscribe to our newsletter.

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address or phone number. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

**What do we use your information for?**

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

  * To personalize your experience  
(your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)

  * To improve our website  
(we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)

  * To improve customer service  
(your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)

  * To send periodic emails

The email address you provide for order processing, may be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order, in addition to receiving occasional company news, updates, related product or service information, etc.

Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.

**How do we protect your information?**

We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required toï¿½keep the information confidential.

After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, social security numbers, financials, etc.) will not be kept on file for more than 60 days.

**Do we use cookies?**

We do use cookies. Cookies are small pieces of data that are stored on your computer, mobile phone or other device. Pixels are small blocks of code on webpages that do things like allow another server to measure viewing of a webpage and are often used in connection with cookies.

We use technologies like cookies, pixels, and local storage (like on your browser or device, which is similar to a cookie but holds more information) to provide and understand a range of products and services.

We use these technologies to do things like:

– make the website easier or faster to use;

– enable features and store information about you (including on your device or in your browser cache) and your use of our website;

– monitor and understand the use of our products and services;

-track referrals so they can compensate a referring student, and,

– protect you, others and us.

For example, we may use these tools to help you use our services, or to know when you are interacting with our partners.

We may ask other partners to serve ads or services to computers, mobile phones or other devices, which may use a cookie, pixel or other similar technology placed by us or the third party (although we would not share information that personally identifies you with an advertiser).

To learn more about how advertisers generally use cookies and the choices advertisers provide, visit the Network Advertising Initiative, the Digital Advertising Alliance, the Internet Advertising Bureau (US), or the Internet Advertising Bureau (EU).

Refer to your browser or device’s help material to learn what controls you can often use to remove or block cookies or other similar technologies or block or remove other data stored on your computer or device (such as by using the various settings in your browser). If you do this, it may affect your ability to use the website or other websites and apps.

**Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

**Third party links**

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

**California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.

**Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

**Online Privacy Policy Only**

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

**Your Consent**

By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy, including our use of cookies.

**Changes to our Privacy Policy**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.

This policy was last modified on 12/14/2016.

**Contacting Us**

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.

_Copyright Next Step Test Preparation 2018_.
